Inventory of the Warner T. Jones 1819-1891
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence, 1855-1891, n.d. (Box 1-2)
  - Letters, 1880-1889., 83 items. (Box-folder 2:135-220)
    - Kirkpatrick & Blackford, Lynchburg, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 22 Nov. 1883., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:144)
      Enclosure: Stamped envelope addressed to Kirkpatrick & Blackford.
    - Anne L. Rutherford, Pampatike, Manquin Post Office, King W[illia]m County, Virginia, to Warner [T.] Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Gloucester County, Virginia, 29 Feb. 1884., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:145)
    - J. Prosser Tabb, Baltimore, [Md.], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 25 Aug. 1884., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:146)
    - Seth F. Miller, Mathews C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, White Marsh P[ost] O[ffice], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 18 Feb. 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:147)
    - E. H. Dabney, New York, [N.Y.], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 2 May 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:148)
    - Robert Colgate, New York, [N.Y.], to William Seldon, Norfolk, Virginia, 9 May 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:149)
    - G. C. Shield, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 22 May 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:150)
    - Warren & Quarles, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use, Virginia], 30 May 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:151)
    - Warren & Quarles, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 6 June 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:152)
    - A. V. Hays, Prices Branch, Montgomery County, Mo., to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester Court House, Gloucester County, Virginia, 15 June 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:153)
    - Th[omas] Croxton, Tappahannock, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[our]t Ho[use], Virginia, 22 June 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:154)
    - S. Slingerland, Sassafras P[ost] O[ffice], Glou[cester] Co[unty], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 29 June [18]85., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:155)
    - Th[omas] Croxton, Tappahannock, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] Ho[use], Virginia, 10 July 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:156)
    - P. M. Thompson, Williamsburg, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, White Marsh, Gloucester County, Virginia, 20 July 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:157)
    - W[illia]m A. Saunders, Cariton's Store, [King and Queen County], Virginia to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 13 Aug. 1885., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:158)
    - A. R. Micou, Tappahannock, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 14 Aug. 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:159)
    - Walker Jones, Newton, King and Queen Co[unty, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 21 Aug. 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:160)
    - J[ohn] R[andolph] Tucker, Lexington, Virginia, to B. F. Bland, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 3 Sept. 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:161)
    - Geo[rge] B. Harrison, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 10 Sept. 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:162)
    - Th[omas] Croxton, Tappahannock, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] Ho[use], Virginia, 16 Sept. 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:163)
    - G. T. Garnett, Mathews C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 16 Sept. 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:164)
    - Warren & Quarles, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 22 Sept. 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:165)
    - N. B. Brooks, Clay Bank, [Gloucester County], Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 28 Sept. 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:166)
    - Frederick W. Power, Richmond, Virginia, W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] Ho[use], Virginia, 28 Sept. 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:167)
    - R. B. Chaffin & Co., Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 29 Sept. 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:168)
    - W.W. Scott, Secretary, State Democratic Executive Committee, Alexandria, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 5 Oct. 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:169)
    - L.Q. Washington, Washington, D.C., to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Court House, Virginia, 9 Oct. 1885., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:170)
    - W. D. Chapman, Woods X[Cross] Roads, Gloucester County, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 13 Oct. 1885., 2 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:171)
    - N. B. Brooks, Clay Bank, [Gloucester County], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 13 Oct. 1885., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:172)
    - W.W. Scott, Secretary, State Democratic Executive Committee, Alexandria, Virginia, to "Dear Sir," n.p., 14 Oct. 1885., 1 page. L. (Box-folder 2:173)
    - James H. Dooley, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 26 Oct. 1885., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:174)
    - Jo[h]n R. Page, University of Virginia, Albemarle County, [Charlottesville], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 25 Nov. 1885., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:176)
    - Susie V. P. Tabb, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse, Virginia], to Judge [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 20 [?] [18]86., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:177)
    - Sam[ue]l B. Chapman, Gloucester County, [Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester County, Virginia, 4 Jan. 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:178)
    - G. T. Garnett, Mathews C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 5 Jan. 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:179)
    - John Tabb, P. O. Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 16 Jan. 1886., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:180)
    - John B. Donovan, Mathews Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 2 Feb. 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:181)
      Enclosure: Report of the Hampton Oyster Convention, held Dec. 16, 1885... to the General Assembly, by John B. Donovan. 12 pp.
    - H. A. Tabb, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 9 Feb. 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:182)
    - B. A. Marsden, Norfolk, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 23 Feb. 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:183)
    - John Tabb, P. O. Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, to Judge [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 25 Feb. 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:184)
    - L. B. Wharton, Taylorsville, Hanover Co[unty], Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester Court House, Virginia, 6 March 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:185)
    - John Tabb, P. O. Gloucester Court House, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 13 Mar. 1886., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:186)
    - E. W. James, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Court House, Virginia, 16 Mar. [18]86., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:187)
    - E. W. James, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Court House, Virginia, 26 Mar. [18]86., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:188)
      Enclosure: B. F. Bland, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, to Dr. E. W. James, n.p. 2 pp. ALS.
    - Th[omas] Croxton, Washington, D.C., to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] Ho[use], Virginia, 2 April 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:189)
    - L. B. Wharton, Taylorsville, Hanover Co[unty], Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 17 April 1886., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:190)
    - Th[omas] Croxton, Washington, D. C. to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] Ho[use], Virginia, 3 June 1886., 2 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:191)
    - A. W. C. Waller, Alexandria, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] House, Gloucester County, Virginia, 20 June 1886., 2 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:192)
    - L. B. Wharton, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 26 June 1886., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:193)
    - Leah S. T[aliaferro], Belle Ville, [Gloucester County, Virginia], to her cousin, Warner T. Jones, Lands End, Gloucester C[ourt] House, Virginia, 20 Aug. 1886., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:194)
    - W.W. Woodward, Saluda, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 23 Aug 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:195)
    - Warren & Quarles, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 1 Sept. 1886., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:196)
    - Jennie Deans Mayer, Rosewell [Gloucester County, Virginia], to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 11 Dec. [1886]., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:197)
    - Warner T. Jones, Land's End, Gloucester County, Virginia, to Jennie Deans Mayer, n.p., 27 Dec. [18]86., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:198)
    - J. H. Fitzhugh, Austin, Texas, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[our]t Ho[use], Virginia, 4 Jan. 1887., 4 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:199)
    - Cha[rle]s T. O'Ferrall, Wash[ington], D.C., to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 25 Feb. 1887., 1 page. ALS. Postal card. (Box-folder 2:200)
    - Warner T. Jones, Lands End, Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, to John R. Page, University of Virginia, [Charlottesville, Virginia], March 1887., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:201)
    - Warren & Quarles, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 14 May 1887., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:202)
    - [Warner T. Jones], Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, to Postmaster at Crittenden, Nansemond Co[unty], Virginia, 25 June 1887., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:203)
    - John C. Williams, Richmond, Virginia, to James Dabney, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 9 Feb. 1888., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:204)
    - E. C. Kenney, Truxton, N[ew] Y[ork], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 22 June [18]88., 1 page. ALS. Postal card. (Box-folder 2:205)
      Re: College of William & Mary.
    - Hugh Stockdell Bird, Petersburg, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 26 June 1888., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:206)
    - G. W. A. Lyon, Portsmouth, O[hio], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 26 June 1888., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:207)
      Re: letter to Jones as a member of the Board of Visitors of William and Mary College and Lyon's desire to be considered for the vacancy of the Chair of Natural Science.
    - Sam[ue]l D. Puller, Norfolk, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Gloucester Co[unty], Virginia, 27 June 1888., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:208)
    - Lyon G. Tyler, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Gloucester County, Virginia, 21 July 1888., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:209)
    - Junius E. Leigh, Richmond, Virginia, to Board of Visitors, College of William & Mary, Williamsburg, Virginia, 23 July 1888., 1 page. TL. (Box-folder 2:210)
      Re: Presidency at the College of William & Mary. Including reference letters for Junius E. Leigh dating from 8 Aug. 1873 to 17 Aug. 1888. 9 TLs. & 3 ALsS.
    - P. M. Thompson, Williamsburg, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Court House, Virginia, 2 Aug. 1888., 8 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:211)
      Re: repairs to the buildings and financial affairs of the College of William and Mary.
    - Jo[h]n L. Mercer, Williamsburg, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 5 Aug. 1888., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:212)
    - Richard F. Beirne, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 9 Aug. 1888., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:213)
    - Richard E. Frayser, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] Ho[use], Virginia, 11 Aug. 1888., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:214)
    - P. M. Thompson, Williamsburg, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, n.p., 13 Aug. 1888., 2 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:215)
      Re: repairs to the buildings and the selection of a President for the College of William & Mary.
    - Junius E. Leigh, Howardsville P[ost] O[ffice], Albemarle Co[unty], Virginia, to H. E. Morecock, Sec[retary to the] Board [of] Visitors, William & Mary College, Williamsburg, Virginia, 17 Aug. 1888., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:216)
      Re: Presidency at the College.
    - Letitia Tyler Semple, Washington, D.C., to Warner [T.] Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Gloucester County, Virginia, 18 Aug. [18]88., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:217)
      Re: Presidency at the College of William & Mary.
    - Junius E. Leigh, Coles Ferry, Charlotte Co[unty], Virginia, to H. E. Morecock, Sec[retary to the] Board of Visitors, W[illiam] & M[ary] College, Williamsburg, Virginia, 27 Aug. 1888., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:218)
    - P. M. Thompson, Williamsburg, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Court House, [Gloucester], Virginia, 17 Jan. 1889., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:220)
  - Letters, 1890-1899., 9 items. (Box-folder 2:222-232)
    - C. Throckmorton, Rosebank, S[taten] I[sland], N[ew] Y[ork], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 4 Jan. 1890., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:222)
    - T. G. Jones, Urbanna, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, n.p., 5 March [18]90., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:223)
    - Joseph Bryan, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 11 March 1890., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:224)
    - Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[ourt] Ho[use], Virginia, to W[illia]m R. Aylett, King William County, Virginia, 14 April 1890., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:225)
    - V. Jefferson Davis, Beauvoir House, [near Biloxi, Mississippi], to Robert Belford, n.p., 7 May 1890., 1 page. PF. (Box-folder 2:226)
    - Joseph Bryan, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 1 January 1891., 1 page. TLS. (Box-folder 2:227)
    - Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, to Polk Miller & Co., Richmond, Virginia, 13 June 1891., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:229)
      Including a note from Polk Miller, Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho use], Virginia (on same page as above) TNS.
    - Joseph Bryan, Richmond, Virginia, to W[arner] T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] H[ouse], Virginia, 19 June 1891., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:230)
    - P. M. Thompson, Culpeper Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 7 Oct. 1891., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:231)
    - W[illia]m B. Taliaferro, Gloucester C[our]t Ho[use, Virginia], to Richard Jones, Lands End, Roanes, Gloucester Co[unty, Virginia], 20 Nov. 1891., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:232)
  - Letters, n.d., 8 items. (Box-folder 2:233-241)
    - J. R. Bryan Doc., n.d., 1 page. ADS. Fragment. (Box-folder 2:233)
    - M. R. H. Garnett, Loyds, Essex [County, Virginia], to [Warner T.] Jones, n.p., 18 April n.y., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:234)
    - R. P. Jones, n.p., to his brother, Warner T. Jones, Wareham, n.d., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:235)
    - Warner T. Jones, n.p., to [?], n.p., n.d., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:236)
    - Warner T. Jones, n.p., to Elizabeth F. Edwards, Matthews County, Virginia, n.d., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:237)
    - W. G. Robins, Abingdon, [Virginia], to Col. [Warner T. Jones], n.p., 9 March n.y., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:238)
      Note: letter was written just before the Civil War.
    - M .B. Seawell, Ladysmede, [Virginia?], to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester C[ourt] House, [Virginia], n.d., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:239)
    - B. R. W[ellford], Jr., Richmond, Virginia, to Warner T. Jones, Gloucester Co[urt] Ho[use], Virginia, 6 Nov. n.y., 1 page. ALS. Postal card. (Box-folder 2:240)
    - Miscellaneous drafts of letters written by Warner T. Jones, n.d., 8 items. (Box-folder 2:241)
  Series 2: Legal Papers
- Legal Papers, 1838-1890 (Box 2-8)
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order by subject or last name.
  - Abingdon, an estate in Gloucester County, Virginia, 1855-1872., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:242)
  - [?] Anderson vs. William H. Anderson, et als. - Suit, 1885., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:243)
    Suit in Gloucester County, Virginia.
  - [?] Ash vs. Pell - Suit, 1852-1861., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:244)
  - Elijah Barnum estate, 1853-1886., 26 items. (Box-folder 3:245)
    Mathews County, Virginia.
  - Henry Belvin vs. John A. B. Thornton, et als. - Suit, 1867., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:246)
  - Peter W. Billups estate, 1838-1853., 64 items. (Box-folder 3:247)
    Gloucester County, Virginia.
  - William Billups estate, 1845-1852., 27 items. (Box-folder 3:248)
    Gloucester County.
  - Bloodgood & Co. vs. Peyton G. Williams - Suit, 1851., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:249)
    Suit in Gloucester Co.
  - Cary Booker estate, 1835-1844., 32 items. (Box-folder 3:250)
  - William Booker estate, 1838-1851., 21 items. (Box-folder 3:251)
  - Hannah K. Breedon - Descent of title, 1884., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:252)
    Descent of title to certain property in Richmond, Virginia.
  - Brown, Hogg, & Jenkins - Invoice, 27 July n.y., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:253)
  - John R. Bryan - Accounts, 1868-1869., 8 items. (Box-folder 3:524)
  - Henry Burton estate, 1831-1845., 17 items. (Box-folder 3:255)
  - Mary Burton guardianship, 1837- 1850., 13 items. (Box-folder 3:256)
  - Simon Burton guardianship, 1837-1849., 9 items. (Box-folder 3:257)
  - Charles Caffee estate, 1851-1856., 25 items. (Box-folder 3:258)
  - [?] Carter vs. [?] Waterman, Sheriff, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:259)
  - E.B.C. Cary - Invoice for purchases, 1861., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:260)
  - George T. Catlett estate, 1858-1872., 9 items. (Box-folder 3:261)
  - Frances Chapman estate, 1843-1857., 26 items. (Box-folder 3:262)
  - James M. Clarke estate, 1844-1858., 68 items. (Box-folder 3:263)
  - John R. Coats, n.d., 1 item. Draft. (Box-folder 3:264)
  - R. Coke, Jr. Estate, 1850., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:265)
  - Sarah Cook - Memo of taxes, 1849-1850., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:266)
  - Franklin Cooke et als. vs. Catharine P. Thurston et als. - Suit, 1851-1852., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:267)
    Suit in Gloucester County.
  - C.C. Curtis to Mrs. H.P. Sheldon - Bond, 1858., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:268)
  - Miss M.G. Curtis guardianship - Receipt, 1 March 1849., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:269)
    Receipt of C.C. Curtis.
  - Robert C. Curtis, Sheriff of Gloucester County - Accounts, 1842-1849., 33 items. (Box-folder 3:270)
  - James M. Dobson vs. John B. Donovan, administrator, et als. - Suit, 1879-1882., 5 items. (Box-folder 3:271)
  - James M. Dobson vs. Robert H. Stubblefield's administrator - Suit, 1882-1883., 5 items. (Box-folder 3:272)
  - Azariah W. Donoho to Warner T. Jones, trustee for Camper and Bruff of Baltimore, Maryland - Indenture, 1845., 2 items. 2 drafts. (Box-folder 3:273)
    Indenture covering a vessel.
  - Sarah Dunn - Invoice, 1852-1853., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:274)
    Invoice for goods bought from T. H. Hughes & Co.
  - A. F. Dutton vs. [?] Hughes - Suit, 1862-1868 & n.d., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:275)
  - William Edwards - Tax bills, 1850-1851., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:276)
  - Enfield, an estate in Gloucester County - Sale papers, 1874., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:277)
    Papers concerning the sale of Enfield by Warner T. Jones, trustee.
  - [?] Ennis vs. Ennis' Executor - Suit, 1852., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:278)
  - Charles Evans - Settlement, 1890-1891., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:279)
    Settlement of a dispute between Charles Evans and Simon Evans concerning land in Ware Neck, Gloucester County.
  - John C. Field estate, 1859-1878., 23 items. (Box-folder 3:280)
  - William S. Field - Accounts, 1844-1860., 9 items. (Box-folder 3:281)
  - John Foster - Trust deeds, 1885., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:282)
    Items concerning trust deeds covering two tracts of land in Mathews County called Spring Dale and Spring Hill.
  - William Freeman estate, 1850-1869., 14 items. (Box-folder 3:283)
  - John Gaines estate, 1835-1849., 10 items. (Box-folder 3:284)
    Middlesex County.
  - James S. Garrison et als. vs. Alfred Palmer et als. - Suit, 1852., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:285)
  - John Godfrey vs. William R. Singleton - Suit, 1851., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:286)
  - David Griffin - Papers relating to a pension claim, n.d., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:287)
    Papers relating to the pension claim filed by the mother of David Griffin, a negro soldier who enlisted in the United States Army, at Yorktown, Virginia, in 1863.
  - Mary G. Hall guardianship, 1846-1850., 20 items. (Box-folder 3:288)
  - A. V Hayes - Memoranda, 1874-1879., 5 items. (Box-folder 3:289)
    Memoranda of lands sold by A. V. Hayes.
  - Georgia B. Hayes and Andrew J. Rowe and Richard H. Hogg - Agreement, 1871., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:290)
    Agreement concerning the lease of a tract of land in Gloucester County called Hook Farm.
  - Joel Hayes estate, 1856-1886. (Box-folder 4:291-300)
    - Joel Hayes estate - Legal papers, 1868-1886., 69 items. (Box-folder 4:291)
      Joel Hayes et als. vs. Susan Hayes et als. Suit in Gloucester County, concerning the administration of the estate of Joel Hayes by John A. B. Thornton.
    - Joel Hayes estate - Suit and accounts, 1867-1881., 95 items. (Box-folder 4:292)
      Joel Hayes et als. vs. Susan Hayes et als. Suit in Gloucester County, concerning the administration of the estate of Joel Hayes by John A. B. Thornton. Accounts.
    - Joel Hayes estate - Suits, 1866-1868., 14 items. (Box-folder 4:293)
      Joel Hayes et als. vs. Susan Hayes et als. Suit in Gloucester County, concerning the administration of the estate of Joel Hayes by John A. B. Thornton. Miscellaneous suits.
    - Joel Hayes estate - Accounts and invoices, 1856-1878., 82 items. (Box-folder 4:294)
    - Joel Hayes estate - Accounts and invoices, 1858-1868., 29 items. (Box-folder 4:295)
      Thomas H. Hughes & Co., merchants. Accounts & invoices. Note: Joel Hayes was a partner in this firm.
    - Joel Hayes estate, 1860-1876., 23 items. (Box-folder 4:296)
      Joel Hayes & Co. Saw Mill.
    - Joel Hayes estate, 1859-1874., 8 items. (Box-folder 4:297)
      Hayes & Rowe. Saw Mill.
    - Joel Hayes estate, 1861., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:298)
      Hayes, Rowe & Co. Saw Mill.
    - Joel Hayes estate - accounts and correspondence concerning the saw mill, 1856-1875., 14 items. (Box-folder 4:299)
      Hayes, Rowe & Thornton. Saw Mill. Accounts and correspondence.
    - Joel Hayes estate - Ledger, 1856-1862., 1 item. 228 pages. (Box-folder 4:300)
      Ledger of Hayes, Rowe & Thornton. Saw Mill
  - R. C. Heywood and wife to William B. Heywood's trustee, 1869., 1 item. 4 pages. (Box-folder 5:301)
    Incomplete draft of an indenture of a tract of land in Gloucester County.
  - [?] Hicks vs. Shultice - Suit, Accounts and correspondence, 1872-1889., 5 items. (Box-folder 5:302)
  - John Hogg estate, 1865-1867., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:303)
    Surveyor's plat, 1867 and promissory note 1865.
  - Warner Hogg vs. James Jenkins et als. - Suit, 1869., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:304)
  - Robert Holston vs. Abner F. Dutton et al.; and Benjamin A. Rowe and Thomas J. Hughes vs. Abner F. Dutton et als. - Suits, 1884-1885., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:305)
    Suits in Gloucester County.
  - Thomas H. Hughes estate, 1860-1868., 8 items. (Box-folder 5:306)
  - Peter B. Hughes, assignee of Joel Hayes, vs. John W. Leavit - Suit, 1866., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:307)
  - Peter B. Hughes - Suits, 1866-1872., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:308)
    Suits against Peter B. Hughes for debts. Gloucester County.
  - John Ison estate, 1847-1852., 15 items. (Box-folder 5:309)
  - John W. Jarvis estate, 1861., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:310)
  - Vincent Jenkins - Legal fees, 1858-1860., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:311)
    Legal fees due Wyndham Kemp.